```
1 <html>
2 <body>

BRADLEY JAMES

4 <!-- Aspiring IT Professional -->

5 <telephone="250-864-6432">
7 <email="work@bradley-james.ca">
8 <location="Kelowna, BC">
```

SUMMARY

With years of experience in customer services and a passion for technology I am enthusiastic about playing a supporting role and being a resource to help people learn. Pulling from knowledge gathered in customer facing and people managing roles I have learned to be creative and resolution oriented. Coupled with patience and a gravity to motivate myself and others I look forward to learning new things and sharing that knowledge as I progress. Along the way I will keep playing video games and practicing my Japanese for when I get to go to Japan、ほじめまして

EXPERIENCE

TD Wealth

Admin Assistant

(1) 2016 - Today

- * Greet clients
- * Assist with onboarding and training new hires
- * Accomplished tasks within established timeframes
- * Keep up to date with regulatory compliance
- * Monitor and submit access requests
- * Maintain inventory and help deploy computer assets
- * Provide informal IT support to colleagues

Starbucks

Shift Supervisor

(1) 2013 - 2017

- * Completed store opening and closing procedures
- * Prepared shift summary reports and communicate regularly on goals and progress
- * Trained new employees, delegating daily tasks and responsibilities as needed
- * Responded to and resolved customer questions and concerns

Real Canadian Superstore

Electronics Representative

<u>U</u>2008 - 2013

- * Keep up to date with knowledge of products
- * Balanced and organized cash register
- * Worked independently to set up and maintain merchandised products, aligning to vendor needs

SKILLS

Soft Skills {

Customer Service; People Managing; Solution Oriented; Detailed; Adaptable; Strong Communication; Computer Savvy;

Software {

Word; Excel; VBA; Outlook; Salesforce; Teams; Windows; Android; Google Docs; VS Code; Github; C; HTML: CSS;

STRENGTHS



Creative



Personable



Lifelong learner



Problem solver



Reliable



Experienced

Marusa Marketing

Customer Care Representative

- 2007
- * Troubleshooting customer concerns with mobile
- * Identified potential products to benefit customers existing mobile plans
- * Stay up to date with products and services
- * Meet standards with typing speeds and accuracy

WIS

devices

Inventory Clerk

- <u>(1)</u>2005 2007
- * Used hand-held devices to record and monitor inventory levels
- * Address inaccuracies while completing external audits
- * Adapted to various hours and working locations
- * Assisted with the training of new staff
- * Completed regular testing for typing speed and accuracy

Tim Hortons

Shift Supervisor

<u>\$\begin{aligned} 2004 - 2005 \end{aligned} \]</u>

- * Helped store management meet standards of service and quality in daily operations
- $\ensuremath{^{*}}$ Maintained clean and well-organized production areas
- * Completed store opening and closing procedures
- * Responded to and resolved customer questions and concerns

MY FREE TIME



- VIDEO GAMES
- PLANTS
- HIKING
- TV & MUSIC
- READING
- JAPANESE

Side Projects {

- < bradley-james.ca
- < github
- < <u>OSSU CS degree</u>

EDUCATION

CS50

Harvard University via edX.org 2022-

_

Introduction to computer science

HS Diploma

North Delta Senior Secondary 2004

9 </body>
10 </html>

< <u>linkedin</u> in >